http://www.realrocknews.com/privacy-policy/

Home / Privacy Policy
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.
At RealRockNews.com, we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information that is collected and recorded by RealRockNews.com, and how we use it.
Types of Data Collected
The following types of data may be collected from visitors to this website, either by RealRockNews.com, or our advertising and statistical data collection partners: Site usage data, cookies, and e-mail address (when using the contact form). Data is collected automatically when users visit this site, or may be provided by users voluntarily when they complete the contact form.
Log Files
Like the majority of other Web sites, RealRockNews.com makes use of log files. These files merely log visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting service’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes, but is not limited to: internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
RealRockNews.com uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type, or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. The use of cookies by this website is primarily for identification of visitors, so that they can be remembered by this website, which allows certain user choices and preferences to remain consistent, and improve the experience of using this website.
The visitor assumes responsibility for the personal data of third parties published or shared through this website, and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the website operator of all responsibility.
We may use a variety of cookies on this site. If you are unfamiliar with cookies, or how to control or remove them, it is recommended that you visit http://www.aboutcookies.org for more information.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on RealRockNews.com.
Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to RealRockNews.com and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/
Google AdSense
This is a cookie that is utilized by Google to report to us how the advertisements shown on RealRockNews.com are performing. User data is anonymous. You can find out more about Google and its policies with regard to advertising at: http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a service that is provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”) for website operators that allows for the collection of visitor usage data. The Google Analytics service is employed by this website so that we can understand how visitors use and interact with it. This data can be used to improve visitor experience. Data collected is anonymous. Google may, at its discretion, make use of the data collected to contextualize and personalize advertisements from its own advertising network.
Google Analytics anonymizes visitor IP addresses where it is appropriate and necessary. This is accomplished by shortening visitor’s IP addresses within member states of the European Union, or in other contracting states to the agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full and complete IP address be sent to a Google server and then shortened for visitors within the United States of America.
Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting is also used here on RealRockNews.com. You can opt out by visiting: https://www.google.com/settings/ads
Users can completely block Google Analytics tracking by using Google’s Analytics Opt-out browser add-on which can be obtained by visiting: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
You can learn more about Google’s privacy policy as it applies to its analytics service by visiting: http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html
Social Buttons
There are pages on this website where “social buttons” may appear. These allow visitors to share or bookmark the pages on this website. There may buttons for: Twitter, Google+, Facebook, LinkedIn, and others that are similar.
These buttons function by connecting to the relevant websites that are associated with these buttons, where there are scripts from those websites that are not under the control of RealRockNews.com. You should know that these websites may be collecting information about your internet usage, including your activities here on RealRockNews.com. In some cases, the sites associated with these buttons will be recording your visit here on RealRockNews.com, including the specific pages you are visiting, even if you do not click on the button.
It is recommended that you review the respective policies of each of these sites to ensure that you understand how they use your information, and to learn how to opt out, or remove this type of information.
Contact Form
Data supplied on our contact form is submitted voluntarily, and any visitors using the contact form authorize the operators of RealRockNews.com to make use of supplied information and data in order to respond to requests from visitors for information. Personal data collected on the contact form includes name and e-mail address.
External Web Services
We may use external web services on RealRockNews.com, mostly to include content on our webpages. For example, we may use the services of sites like YouTube and Vimeo to display video content. This is not an exhaustive or complete list of the services we may use now, or may use in the future when including content from other websites. As is the case with the social buttons, we cannot prevent these websites from collecting information on your use of this included content.
Our Advertising Partners
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:
Google
Each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site, and you can find links to the privacy policies of our advertising partners on this page.
You may consult this listing to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of RealRockNews.com.
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on RealRockNews.com and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.
RealRockNews.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Third Party Privacy Policies
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices, as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. RealRockNews.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of other advertisers or websites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites or help documentation.
Children’s Information
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.
RealRockNews.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that RealRockNews.com has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact link in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website, and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
Legal Action
Any data collected collected here from visitors to this website is subject to use by legal authorities who could demand access in accordance with applicable laws or court rulings. All visitors should be aware that any of this data may be required by by legal authorities for the purpose of identifying them during the course of legal action.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.
We operate this site on an “implied consent” basis, which means that we assume you are satisfied. If you are not satisfied, then you should discontinue your use of this site, or you should remove all cookies that may have populated your computer as a result of visiting this site. You may also browse this site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (labeled as “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, “Private Browsing” in Firefox and Safari etc.) Consult your browser’s help page or documentation for further information.
Visitor’s Rights
Visitors to this site have the right to know whether or not personal data regarding their activity here has been stored. Visitors may contact the site operators to inquire about the contents of the data and how it was collected, to verify that it is accurate, or to ask that information to be supplemented, deleted, removed, or corrected. Inquires and requests may be sent using the contact information included elsewhere on this page.
Update
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Friday, June 30, 2015.
Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.
Leave a reply CancelYour email address will not be published. Required fields are marked *
Your comment (required):
Name (required):
Email (required):
